Are you an account holder of AAA Bank? Have
you been told that you will get AAA Health
Shield 360 for ₹1? But about AAA
Health Advantage
₹2000000?
AAA Health Shield 360 is a bank
based group policy and these are the
advantages and disadvantages of bank based
group policies. Point number one: Low
premium. The premiums of bank based policies are
always low. Point number two:
You get them without any medical checkup.
Point number three: Even if you have a
very serious pre-existing disease,
you get this health insurance policy.
Now what are the disadvantages
of these policies? Point number one: There is
no life long renewability in these policies
and if the claims become high, the insurer can
terminate this policy. Point
number two: The terms and conditions of this policy can be
changed abruptly at any time
without informing you. Point number three: The
premium of these policies can be increased very steeply.
Without telling you,
which policy should you buy, for example,
Health Shield 360 is cheap but its features are
such that it does not give you life long renewability
and is harmful for you in the long term,
so always buy a personal policy
and never buy a bank based health insurance
policy,
is your policy a bank based group policy or a
personal health insurance policy,
tell me in the comments